Guide to the Transgender Erotic Pulp Fiction Collection from the Series Transvestite Tales
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Transgender erotic pulp fiction collection from the series Transvestite tales
1988-1994
Bailey 9
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
1
52 v.; 18 cm.
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing.
Bailey, Laura E., 1951-
Star Distributors, Ltd
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing.
Some individual titles (see accompanying list) taken from cover.
All individual titles paperbound.
Cross-dressers -- Fiction; Cross-dressing -- Fiction; Transgender people -- Fiction; Bisexuals -- Fiction; Bondage (Sexual behavior) -- Fiction; Sex -- Fiction; Sexual dominance and submission -- Fiction; Erotic stories; Erotica -- New York (State) -- New York -- 20th Century; LGBTQ resource; Bailey, Laura E., 1951- -- Ownership
- Transvestite Tales
  - A guy with tits, c1988; TT_101_ (Box 101-134)
    Scope and Contents
    Stamp on top edge: 86 [?].
  - TV nun, c1988; TT_102_ (Box 101-134)
  - TV hostage, c1988; TT_103_ (Box 101-134)
    Inventory/price label on cover: 3502 37 for $3.95
  - Transvestite mistress, c1988; first printing 1982; TT_104_ (Box 101-134)
    Inventory label (?) on back cover with ms. number: 38 [?]
  - TV soap star, c1989; TT_105_ (Box 101-134)
  - TV gymnast, c1989; TT_106_ (Box 101-134)
  - Belle with balls, c1989; TT_107_ (Box 101-134)
  - TV whipmistress, c1989; first printing 1982; TT_108_ (Box 101-134)
  - TV secretary, c1989; TT_109_ (Box 101-134)
  - TV undercover, c1989; TT_110_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on top edge: MBI
  - TV training school, c1989; TT_111_ (Box 101-134)
  - Transvestite maid, c1989; first printing 1982; TT_112_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on top edge: 117 [?].
  - The maid's a man, c1989; TT_113_ (Box 101-134)
    "Stamp on top edge: 33 Barcode label on p. [1]"
  - TV hooker, c1989; TT_114_ (Box 101-134)
  - TV blind date, c1989; TT_115_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on bottom edge: CBD
  - Transvestite tease, c1989; first printing 1980; TT_116_ (Box 101-134)
  - She-male fantasies, c1989; TT_117_ (Box 101-134)
    "Stamp on bottom edge: 46 Barcode label on p. [1]"
  - TV nurse, c1989; TT_118_ (Box 101-134)
  - Tied transvestite, c1989; TT_119_ (Box 101-134)
  - Hospital transvestite, c1989; first printing 1983; TT_120_ (Box 101-134)
    Undeciphered stamp on bottom edge
  - Victoria, TV, c1990; TT_121_ (Box 101-134)
  - Stacked like me, c1990; TT_122_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on top edge: Model Dist.
  - TV slave, c1990; TT_123_ (Box 101-134)
  - Serving sisters, c1990; first printing 1983; TT_124_ (Box 101-134)
  - Crossing the line, c1990; TT_125_ (Box 101-134)
    Price label on front cover, obscuring printed price: $3.94
  - Tasty Timmy, c1990; TT_126_ (Box 101-134)
    Inventory (?) label on front cover: 9/05/90 414706
  - Corsets and studs, c1990; TT_127_ (Box 101-134)
    Inventory (?) labe on front cover: 9/05/90 414707
  - The banker's secret, c1990; first printing 1981; TT_128_ (Box 101-134)
  - Changing partners, c1990; TT_129_ (Box 101-134)
  - Initiation night, c1990; TT_130_ (Box 101-134)
  - Switch 'n mix, c1990; TT_131_ (Box 101-134)
  - Dominant transvestite, c1990; first printing 1982; TT_132_ (Box 101-134)
  - Tom, c1991; TT_133_ (Box 101-134)
  - Tami, c1991; TT_134_ (Box 101-134)
  - Kristen, c1991; TT_135_ (Box 135-152)
    Faded stamp on top edge: 09 [?]
  - TV starlet, c1991; first printing 1988; TT_136_ (Box 135-152)
  - Dan's dilemma, c1991; TT_137_ (Box 135-152)
    Stamp on bottom edge: SODI
  - Robyn's little girl, c1991; TT_138_ (Box 135-152)
    Stamp on top edge: 52
  - The "girl" next door, c1991; TT_139_ (Box 135-152)
    "Stamp on top edge: 36 Barcode label on p. [1], partially obscuring printed advertisement, and p. [149]"
  - TV undercover, c1991; first printing 1989; TT_140_ (Box 135-152)
  - That's no lady, c1992; first printing 1988; TT_141_ (Box 135-152)
  - Cross dressed whimp, c1992; first printing 1981; TT_142_ (Box 135-152)
  - Panties with bulges, c1992; first printing 1986; TT_143_ (Box 135-152)
  - TV in training, c1992; first printing 1988; TT_144_ (Box 135-152)
  - Glenda, c1993; first printing 1986 under title "TV biker"; TT_145_ (Box 135-152)
    Stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist.
  - Raye, c1993; first printing 1987 under title "TV waitress"; TT_146_ (Box 135-152)
  - Loretta, c1993; first printing 1988; TT_147_ (Box 135-152)
  - Danielle, c1993; first printing 1990 under title "Corsets and studs"; TT_148_ (Box 135-152)
  - Serving sisters, c1994; first printing 1983, reprinted 1990; TT_149_ (Box 135-152)
  - Tasty Timmy, c1994; first printing 1990; TT_150_ (Box 135-152)
  - Needing it, c1994; first printing 1990; TT_151_ (Box 135-152)
  - Silk and lace, c1994; first printing 1986; TT_152_ (Box 135-152)